<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>
    <string name="tourguide">/tourguideapp</string>
    <string name="tourguideapp">tourguideapp</string>

    <string name="category_history">History</string>
    <string name="category_city">City</string>
    <string name="category_accommodation">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="category_tours">Tours</string>

    <string name="tour_guide">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="category_enter">Enter the category</string>

    <string name="history_of_legnica">History of Legnica</string>
    <string name="city_outlook">City outlook</string>
    <string name="accommodation">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="food_facilities">Food facilities</string>
    <string name="city_nature">City nature</string>
    <string name="regional_trips">Regional trips</string>

    <string name="category_history_description">Owing to wealthy history, Legnica became an old city with unique atmosphere.
        Above 1000 years of official existence left a great imprint on it’s culture and architecture. During 500 years it was ruled by Piast dynasty.
        Apart from that it was under rule of Czech dynasty, Habsburgs, Prussia and Germany.</string>
    <string name="category_city_description">Between 1 June 1975 and 31 December 1998 Legnica became the capital of the Voivodeship.
        Now it’s the seat of the county and since 1992 it is also the seat of Diocese. Currently about 100000 inhabitants live here.
        In 1950s and 1960 copper and nickel deposits began to be excavated, changing totally regional economy.</string>
    <string name="category_accommodation_description">Legnica offers a wide variety od accommodation places for all visitors and all budgets.
        Situated mainly within the center area of the city will satisfy almost everyone. </string>
    <string name="category_food_description">There’s a great variety of restaurants, pubs or inns in Legnica. 
        There are locals offering typical polish meals and places where you can eat pizza or oriental food. 
        All tastes and budgets will be satisfied. </string>
    <string name="category_nature_description">Legnica is admired for it’s gardens and parks. The city can boast with above 700 hectares of green space which is about 10% of it’s whole surface.
        In the center of the city there’s a huge 58 hectares park with small palm house and nice pond. Spare time can be also spent on the Kaczawa river banks.</string>
    <string name="category_trips_description">Well communication facilities make Legnica a good place to start trips around region of Lower Silesia.
        This historical area is full of very interesting places to visit. Below you can find just a few 1 day or weekend trips.
        However I assure you that there is much more place worth seeing. </string>

    <string name="h1">Early history</string>
    <string name="h2">First Slavic tribes</string>
    <string name="h3">Battle of Legnica</string>
    <string name="h4">Duchy of Legnica</string>
    <string name="h5">Holy Roman Empire</string>
    <string name="h6">Second battle of Legnica</string>
    <string name="h7">Congress of Vienna</string>
    <string name="h8">Treaty of Versailles</string>
    <string name="h9">Potsdam conference</string>
    <string name="h10">Cold War</string>

    <string name="h1_desc">First documented historical sources of settlement come from this place about 1850 years ago.
        A few hundred years later before written evidences – there was a small castle situated in the east part hills.
        The settlement belonged to the Lusatian culture.
        In the Romanian times the city was called Lugidunum and existed as the capital of tribe Lugii. It was situated on the antic map of Ptolemy.</string>
    <string name="h2_desc">Slavic tribes moved into that area around 8th century. Official reference in the cronicles come from 1004.
        The city name is firstly mentioned in 1149 in the document of High Duke of Poland Boleslaw IV the Curly.
        Most likely Legnica became his residence. The city started to grow being the fundamental point of trading paths for Europe of Middle Ages.</string>
    <string name="h3_desc">Legnica became famous city because of the great battle at Legnickie Pole. It was the time of Mongol invasion of Europe.
        Combined armies of polish duke Henry II the Pious of Silesia, Bavarian miners, Czech troops and military orders were defeated.
        Mongols killed Henry and destroyed united forces. As a result his coutry collapsed.</string>
    <string name="h4_desc">At the beginning of 14th century Legnica became the capital of the Duchy. It was one of the most important cities in Central Europe
        with population reaching almost 16000 inhabitants. Quick growth of the city started after the discovery of gold in the Kaczawa River between Legnica and Zlotoryja.
        This great city expansion stopped after a huge fire which totally devastated all wooden buildings.</string>
    <string name="h5_desc">During 14th century Legnica became vassal of the Kingdom of Bohemia and it was absorbed by Holy Roman Empire.
        Around 1522 the citizens converted into Lutheranism. After the death of King Louis II of Hungary and Bohemia Legnica became the part of the Habsburg Monarchy of Austria.</string>
    <string name="h6_desc">In 1742 Legnica, along with most of Silesia, became the part of Kingdom of Prussia.
        It was a result of King Frederick the Great\'s victory over Austria  in the War of the Austrian Succession.
        Seven years’s war bringed in 1760 the great Battle of Legnica where Frederick’s defeated an Austrian army. </string>
    <string name="h7_desc">In 1813 Prussian army led by Field Marshal Blücher defeated Napoleonic forces in the Battle of Katzbach.
        By the provisions of Congress of Vienna Legnica and the surrounding territory were absorbed by the Province of Silesia on the 1st May 1816.
        In 1874 the city became the part of German Empire. </string>
    <string name="h8_desc">Until 1945 by the provisions of, following Word War I, Treaty of Versailles Legnica became the part of Province of Lower Silesia.</string>
    <string name="h9_desc">In 1945 Nazi Germany was defeated and World War II was over. Following Potsdam Conference incorporated Legnica and all east Silesia to Poland.
        German citizens were expelled and replaced with Poles.
        During the war the city was only slightly demaged. However until 1965 most parts of the old town buildings were destroyed, bringing rebuilt, modern form.</string>
    <string name="h10_desc">After the World War II Soviet forces in Poland situated headquarters in Legnica. This fact left a great imprint on city’s life.
        Now it was divided into Polish and Soviet parts. In april 1945 it is etimated that there were about 16000 Polish, 12000 German and 60000 Soviet citizens.
        Soviets left the city finally in 1993.</string>

    <string name="h1_img_desc">Lusatian culture</string>
    <string name="h2_img_desc">Boleslaw IV the Curly</string>
    <string name="h3_img_desc">Battle of Legnica</string>
    <string name="h4_img_desc">gold</string>
    <string name="h5_img_desc">Holy Roman Empire</string>
    <string name="h6_img_desc">Battle of Legnica</string>
    <string name="h7_img_desc">Napoleon Bonaparte</string>
    <string name="h8_img_desc">Newspaper</string>
    <string name="h9_img_desc">Potsdam Conference</string>
    <string name="h10_img_desc">Graves of soviet solders</string>

    <string name="c1">Cathedral of Sts. Peter and Paul</string>
    <string name="c2">New Town Hall</string>
    <string name="c3">Modjeska Theatre</string>
    <string name="c4">Hospital</string>
    <string name="c5">Piast Castle</string>
    <string name="c6">Copper Museum of Legnica</string>
    <string name="c7">Tenement Houses</string>
    <string name="c8">Gas Tower</string>
    <string name="c9">Railway Station</string>
    <string name="c10">City Stadium</string>

    <string name="c1_desc">Magnificent cathedral was built in 1333 – 1380 and in 15th century the chapels were attached to the side naves.
        Serious rebuild occurred in 1892 – 94 when the temple received Neogotic style.In 25 March 1992 John Paul II sacrifised it as a cathedral.</string>
    <string name="c2_desc">The Town Hall was built in neo renaissance style in 1905. Currently it is headquarters of municipality in Legnica.</string>
    <string name="c3_desc">The building of new theatre was ready on Christmas 1842. It had 500 seat and there were always queues of ticket buyers.
        After the World War II the theatre was totally destroyed. It started up again in 1977. In 1994 Jacek Glomb began to work as a Chief.
        His innovative approach brought a great fame in country and on the international field.</string>
    <string name="c4_desc">The hospital in Legnica was opened in 1989. It’s the largest employer in the city employing over 1100 people.
        It’s divided into 24 departments with over 600 beds. It services annually over 100000 patients.</string>
    <string name="c5_desc">A stronghold was erected in 1230s and it was one of the first such castles in Poland. The initiator of the building was Henry I the Bearded.
        The castle was the residence for the Dukes of Legnica until 1675. It had been rebuilt several times, most significantly by Frederick II.
        In the 19th century it was reconstructed after a fire. Currently it houses several educational institutions.</string>
    <string name="c6_desc">It was built in 1728 in Baroque style. It contains the collections associated with excavation, processing and usage of copper.
        Currently there are over 30000 exhibits and 8200 volumens in the library.</string>
    <string name="c7_desc">The most probably it was built in 1574. There are 4 renaissance and 4 classical houses.
        Stylish diversification is the effect of many reconstructions which affected these buildings during next centuries. </string>
    <string name="c8_desc">It was founded in 1856 and in the beginning lighted about 250 lamps in the city.
        It had been rebuilt several times, lastly in 1917 when ammonia tower was added.</string>
    <string name="c9_desc">It has been opened in 1844 and it’s the main station wfor Legnica, being the beginning of the line to Katowice, Jerzmanice-Zdroj and Rudna.
        It services all kinds of passing trains. Currently it has B category which means that it services annually 1 – 2 milions of passengers.</string>
    <string name="c10_desc">It was completely rebuiled in 2005. Modernisation brought additional lights, corners, heated turf, full roofing and electronic management and control system.</string>

    <string name="c1_img_desc">Cathedral of Sts. Peter and Paul</string>
    <string name="c2_img_desc">New Town Hall</string>
    <string name="c3_img_desc">Modjeska Theatre</string>
    <string name="c4_img_desc">Hospital</string>
    <string name="c5_img_desc">Piast Castle</string>
    <string name="c6_img_desc">Copper Museum of Legnica</string>
    <string name="c7_img_desc">Tenement Houses</string>
    <string name="c8_img_desc">Gas Tower</string>
    <string name="c9_img_desc">Railway Station</string>
    <string name="c10_img_desc">City Stadium</string>

    <string name="a1">Qubus Hotel</string>
    <string name="a2">Hotel Palacyk</string>
    <string name="a3">Kamieniczka Hotel</string>
    <string name="a4">Sekowski Hotel</string>
    <string name="a5">Arkadia Hotel</string>
    <string name="a6">Gwarna Hotel</string>
    <string name="a7">Milenium Hotel</string>
    <string name="a8">Rezydencja Hotel</string>
    <string name="a9">Youth Hostel</string>

    <string name="a1_address">Skarbowa 2\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a2_address">Tadeusza Kosciuszki 37\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a3_address">Mlynarska 15_16\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a4_address">Gliwicka 15\n59200 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a5_address">Gliwicka 6\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a6_address">Wjazdowa 12\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a7_address">Chojnowska 150\n59200 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a8_address">Stefana Okrzei 18\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="a9_address">Henryka Jordana 17\n59220 Legnica</string>

    <string name="a1_www">https://www.qubushotel.com/</string>
    <string name="a2_www">http://www.hotelpalacyk.pl/</string>
    <string name="a3_www">http://hotelkamieniczka.pl/</string>
    <string name="a4_www">http://www.hotelsekowski.pl/</string>
    <string name="a5_www">http://www.hotel-arkadia.pl/</string>
    <string name="a6_www">http://www.hotelgwarna.pl/</string>
    <string name="a7_www">http://www.mojhotel.pl/</string>
    <string name="a8_www">http://www.rezydencja-hotel.pl/</string>
    <string name="a9_www">http://www.ssm.legnica.eu/</string>

    <string name="a1_email">legnica@qubushotel.com</string>
    <string name="a2_email">hotelpalacyk@hotelpalacyk.lca.pl</string>
    <string name="a3_email">recepcja@hotelkamieniczka.pl</string>
    <string name="a4_email">recepcja@hotelsekowski.pl</string>
    <string name="a5_email">legnica@hotel-arkadia.pl</string>
    <string name="a6_email">hotel@hotelgwarna.pl</string>
    <string name="a7_email">hotel@mojhotel.pl</string>
    <string name="a8_email">kopcza@rezydencja-hotel.pl</string>
    <string name="a9_email">recepcjassm@legnica.eu</string>

    <string name="a1_phone">Phone: 76 866 21 00</string>
    <string name="a2_phone">Phone: 76 851 25 35</string>
    <string name="a3_phone">Phone: 76 723 73 92</string>
    <string name="a4_phone">Phone: 76 721 31 60</string>
    <string name="a5_phone">Phone: 76 850 78 00</string>
    <string name="a6_phone">Phone: 76 745 00 00</string>
    <string name="a7_phone">Phone: 76 713 53 00</string>
    <string name="a8_phone">Phone: 76 723 08 70</string>
    <string name="a9_phone">Phone: 76 862 54 12</string>

    <string name="a1_img_desc">Qubus Hotel</string>
    <string name="a2_img_desc">Hotel Palacyk</string>
    <string name="a3_img_desc">Kamieniczka Hotel</string>
    <string name="a4_img_desc">Sekowski Hotel</string>
    <string name="a5_img_desc">Arkadia Hotel</string>
    <string name="a6_img_desc">Gwarna Hotel</string>
    <string name="a7_img_desc">Milenium Hotel</string>
    <string name="a8_img_desc">Rezydencja Hotel</string>
    <string name="a9_img_desc">Youth Hostel</string>

    <string name="f1">Tivoli Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f2">Vis a Vis Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f3">Tradycja Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f4">Benvenuti in Italia Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f5">Don Giovanni Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f6">Efez Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f7">Dragon Oriental Bar</string>
    <string name="f8">Piastowska Inn</string>
    <string name="f9">Qubus Hotel Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f10">Rynek 10 Restaurant</string>

    <string name="f1_address">Zlotoryjska 21\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f2_address">Mlynarska 7\n59200 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f3_address">Rynek 9\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f4_address">Najswietszej Marii Panny 9\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f5_address">Najswietszej Marii Panny 1\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f6_address">Najswietszej Marii Panny 9\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f7_address">plac Klasztorny 4\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f8_address">Gwiezdna 4\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f9_address">Skarbowa 2\n59220 Legnica</string>
    <string name="f10_address">Rynek 10\n59200 Legnica</string>

    <string name="f1_www">http://restauracjativoli.pl/</string>
    <string name="f2_www">http://www.restauracja-visavis.pl/</string>
    <string name="f3_www">http://www.tradycja.legnica.pl/</string>
    <string name="f4_www">http://benvenuti.com.pl/</string>
    <string name="f5_www">http://www.dongiovanni.legnica.pl/</string>
    <string name="f6_www">http://efezpolska.pl/</string>
    <string name="f7_www">http://dragon.legnica.pl/</string>
    <string name="f8_www">http://www.restauracjaoberza.pl/</string>
    <string name="f9_www">https://www.qubushotel.com/pl/restauracje/</string>
    <string name="f10_www">http://www.rynek10.com.pl/</string>

    <string name="f1_email">tivoli@iscatering.pl</string>
    <string name="f2_email">visavis@visavis.pl</string>
    <string name="f3_email">tradycja@animak-kopcza.pl</string>
    <string name="f4_email">legnica@benvenuti.com.pl</string>
    <string name="f5_email">dongiovanni@animak-kopcza.pl</string>
    <string name="f6_email">info@efezpolska.pl</string>
    <string name="f7_email">dragon@dragon.pl</string>
    <string name="f8_email">oberza.piastowska@lubinpex.com.pl</string>
    <string name="f9_email">legnica@qubushotel.com</string>
    <string name="f10_email">rynek10@iscatering.pl</string>

    <string name="f1_phone">Phone: 76 862 23 04</string>
    <string name="f2_phone">Phone: 76 722 30 20</string>
    <string name="f3_phone">Phone: 76 852 35 33</string>
    <string name="f4_phone">Phone: 606 354 744</string>
    <string name="f5_phone">Phone: 76 722 81 52</string>
    <string name="f6_phone">Phone: 76 721 33 16</string>
    <string name="f7_phone">Phone: 76 862 30 37</string>
    <string name="f8_phone">Phone: 76 722 22 71</string>
    <string name="f9_phone">Phone: 76 866 21 00</string>
    <string name="f10_phone">Phone: 76 862 30 79</string>

    <string name="f1_img_desc">Tivoli Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f2_img_desc">Vis a Vis Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f3_img_desc">Tradycja Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f4_img_desc">Benvenuti in Italia Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f5_img_desc">Don Giovanni Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f6_img_desc">Efez Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f7_img_desc">Dragon Oriental Bar</string>
    <string name="f8_img_desc">Piastowska Inn</string>
    <string name="f9_img_desc">Qubus Hotel Restaurant</string>
    <string name="f10_img_desc">Rynek 10 Restaurant</string>

    <string name="n1">Park</string>
    <string name="n2">Palm House</string>
    <string name="n3">Kaczawa River</string>
    <string name="n4">Trees Avenue</string>
    <string name="n5">Goat Pond</string>

    <string name="n1_desc">First written sources about park come as early as from 1316 when duke Boleslaw III bought a huge fields nearby the river.
        Developed over the years received today\'s outlook. Park is also popular place of sport and cultural events.</string>
    <string name="n2_desc">It\’s been founded and built in 1898. Palm house has buildings and areas of above 1 hectare. It was badly affected by the flood in 1977.
        Currently reconstructed and rebuild has free admission for everyone who wants to visit it.</string>
    <string name="n3_desc">It springs from Kaczawskie Mountains near Kaczorów and flows through region with Legnica until it reaches Oder river where it empties.
        Total length of the river is 98km (61mi). </string>
    <string name="n4_desc">It’s a natural monument and historical avenue of London plane. Some trees come from 1844 when the avenue was created.
        Plants grow to height of 30m and host many species of birds.</string>
    <string name="n5_desc">It existed as early as in the Middle Ages when was a part of city defence system. Rebuilt over the ages, received today’s outlook in 1929.
        It was partially destroyed during the flood in 1977. Recultivated in 2008 hosts many interesting plants and animals, mainly birds.</string>

    <string name="n1_img_desc">Park</string>
    <string name="n2_img_desc">Palm House</string>
    <string name="n3_img_desc">Kaczawa River</string>
    <string name="n4_img_desc">Trees Avenue</string>
    <string name="n5_img_desc">Goat Pond</string>

    <string name="t1">Swieradow – Zdroj</string>
    <string name="t2">Szczawno - Zdroj</string>
    <string name="t3">Bolkow city</string>
    <string name="t4">Kowary city</string>
    <string name="t5">Ksiaz castle</string>
    <string name="t6">Klodzko city</string>
    <string name="t7">Jelenia Gora</string>
    <string name="t8">Szklarka Poreba</string>
    <string name="t9">Table Mountains</string>
    <string name="t10">Mysliborski Gorge</string>

    <string name="t1_desc">A small town in south – west of Poland, nearby the border with Czech Republic. First written sources about this place come from 1524.
        Known of mineral water springs. In 1899 great pump-room with spa was built on the hills. It offers mineral water, radon and mud bath treatments of rheumatism.
        Fans of skiing will like this town for opened in 2008 gondola.</string>
    <string name="t2_desc">A small town in south – west of Poland, 3km (2mi) from Walbrzych city. First written sources about it come from 1221.
        Because of many mineral water springs present in the city – pump – room with spa was built in 1820.
        Horse lovers will find this place attractive because of stud farms.</string>
    <string name="t3_desc">A small town in south – west of Poland, at the Nysa Szalona River, in the Jawor country. First written sources come from 1276.
        Known of the Bolkow castle and it’s ruins standing above the town. It was built in 13th century. Devastated by the Thirty Years War.</string>
    <string name="t4_desc">A small town in south – west of Poland, 14km from Jelenia Gora. First mentioned in 1148.
        Known of many mineral springs and sanatoriums for different diseases treatment. Fans of toys may note it for expanded miniature park showing
        architectural monuments of the region.</string>
    <string name="t5_desc">A large castle located nearby Walbrzych city. Main attraction of the Walbrzych and whole region. First sources about the castle come from 1263.
        After the World War II used as a sanatorium and cultural place. Currently great part of it is avaiable for sightseeing. </string>
    <string name="t6_desc">A small and old city in the south – west of Poland, in the Klodzko valey, on the Nysa river.
        Received city rights in 1233, however first settlements come from as early as at least 1st century BC. Within ages being the part of different countries.
        Known of large fortress located on the high rock above the city, gothic bridge, tunnels and many more attractions.</string>
    <string name="t7_desc">A city in south – west of Poland, nearby Karkonosze Mountains. Received the city rights in 1288, being the important part of trade routes in those times.
        Known of many historical attractions. Fans of sport will find it very attractive for aviation, cycling, canoo or hiking trail activities.</string>
    <string name="t8_desc">A small town in the south – west of Poland, close to Jelenia Gora city. First written sources come from 1366.
        Known as a great center of mountain hiking, cycling and skiing. There are also many sanatoriums for different diseases treatment.</string>
    <string name="t9_desc">Part of Sudetes Mountains, are 42km mountain range. There’s a National Park located at the area of it.
        Formed mainly of sandstone, contains many strange and interesting rock formations. Very pleasure place for walking.</string>
    <string name="t10_desc">A nature reserve in the south – west of Poland, on the river Jawornik, part of Jawor county. A reserve was established in 1962.
        With total area of 9.72 hectare. Famous and attractive walking destination, with a place to lighting up the fire.</string>

    <string name="t1_img_desc">Swieradow – Zdroj</string>
    <string name="t2_img_desc">Szczawno - Zdroj</string>
    <string name="t3_img_desc">Bolkow castle</string>
    <string name="t4_img_desc">Kowary city</string>
    <string name="t5_img_desc">Ksiaz castle</string>
    <string name="t6_img_desc">Klodzko city</string>
    <string name="t7_img_desc">Jelenia Gora</string>
    <string name="t8_img_desc">Szklarka Poreba</string>
    <string name="t9_img_desc">Table Mountains</string>
    <string name="t10_img_desc">Mysliborski Gorge</string>

    <string name="legnica">Legnica</string>
    <string name="stadium_thumbnail">Stadium thumbnail</string>
    <string name="castle_thumbnail">Castle thumbnail</string>
    <string name="cathedral_thumbnail">Cathedral thumbnail</string>
    <string name="hospital_thumbnail">Hospital thumbnail</string>
    <string name="marketplace_thumbnail">Marketplace thumbnail</string>
    <string name="museum_thumbnail">Museum thumbnail</string>
    <string name="park_thumbnail">Park thumbnail</string>
    <string name="theatre_thumbnail">Theatre thumbnail</string>
    <string name="shield">Shield</string>
    <string name="stamp">Stamp</string>
    <string name="stamp_maker">Stamp maker</string>

    <string name="details_image">Detail image</string>
    <string name="list_image">List image</string>
    <string name="category_image">Category image</string>
    <string name="back_list_button">Back to list button</string>
    <string name="back_category_button">Back to category button</string>
    <string name="list_button">List button</string>
    <string name="enter_button">Enter button</string>
    <string name="search_icon">Search icon</string>
    <string name="details_dialog">Details dialog fragment</string>
</resources>
